## Baby Sivaraj

**Associate** 

## Contact

Phone: +91 6369183538

E-Mail: babyece95@gmail.com

### **Skills**

- C#
- VB
- SQL Server
- MVC
- SSRS
- Crystal Reports
- JQuery
- VB6
- GITHUB
- Azure DEVOPS
- Power BI

#### Personal Skills

- Passionate
- Forward Thinking
- Focused
- Hard Working
- Creativity

## Languages

- Tamil
- English

# **Personal Details**

Date of Birth Nationality Address

05.07.1995 Indian D/O M.Sivaraj, 3/57, Moongiltholuvu, Tiruppur(DT), Tamil Nadu-642 202.

Associate with over 4 years of successful experience in MSSQL server, MVC, C#.net, JQuery, VB.NET. Recognized of consistently for performance excellence and contributions to success in industry. Strengths in SQL server, C# and Crystal Reports, JQuery backed by training in [.Net Core, Azure DEVOPs, Web API]. Energetic and always ahead of time, I have been associated in companies that have benefited from my efficient computer programming and expert analysis.

## **Experience**

#### 02-2021 -Present

Cognizant Technology Solutions, Chennai. [Associate] Project Name: Timesheet

- Expertise in working with technologies like C#.NET, JQuery, MVC, MSSQL Server, GITHUB, Azure DEVOPs
- Involved in enhancing the business layer to provide more interfaces and functions needed for the system Migrated and exported data in various database.
- Created Packages, Procedures, Functions, Triggers, and Cursors using SQL Server.

#### 04-2019 -02-2021

[Analyst Programmer] Ramco Systems – Chennai **Project Name:** Finance

- Worked on Database Design, Implementation and writing SQL Scripts, Stored procedures, user defined functions, complicated queries, Triggers and Views.
- Migrated and exported data in various database. Created Packages, Procedures, Functions, Triggers, and Cursors using SQL Server.

#### 08-2017 -04-2019

PSG Industrial Institute – Coimbatore [Programmer Analyst] **Project Name:** Integrated Accounting System

- Expertise in working with technologies like VB, C#.NET, VB.NET, ASP.NET, SQL Server, Web Service, JavaScript.
- Developed reports using Crystal Reports. Actively involved in developing Complex Reports involving Cross-tab Reports, Sub reports, Charts and Graphs.
- Created, enhanced, maintained essential Crystal Reports and working with reporting tools SSRS.

## **Education**

BE [CSE] - 2017 - 6.37 CGPA

PSG College of Technology, Coimbatore.

**DIPLOMA [ECE] - 2014-99.14 %** 

NV Polytechnic College, Pethappampatti, Tiruppur.

- H.Sc (Higher Secondary Certificate) 2012 66.25%, Government H.Sc. School, Pethappampatti, Tiruppur.
- SSLC (Secondary School Leaving Certificate) 2010 82.8%

Government H.Sc. School, Pethappampatti, Tiruppur.